<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Srijan</string>
    <string name="login_continue">Click here to continue to Home activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_fragment_about">About Us</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="buy_now">Buy Now</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <!-- All about-us strings -->
    <string name="title_about">Srijan</string>
    <string name="subtitle_about">MotoSports</string>
    <string name="about_description">\t\t\tSrijan Motorsports Incorporated is a leading name in India as a
        manufacturer of Formula race cars. The company is a home to innovators with a vision and passion
        in race car design and manufacturing. For almost a decade now, the company has been relentlessly
        working on producing Formula cars to meet the expectations of the people passionate about Formula racing.
        So far, we have successfully launched 6 successive models of race cars.</string>
    <string name="about_latest_model_title">We are all set to launch its latest model, TSI-17.</string>
    <string name="about_tsi117_model">\t\t\tOur model, TSI-17, comes in two chief variations namely, TSI-17
        SE and TSI-17 KE. Along with this, we are giving our customers a chance to “cook up their own race car”.
        This allows you to choose different car components from among the variants provided by us. </string>
    <string name="about_formula_challenge_title">Srijan Formula Challenge</string>
    <string name="about_formula_challenge_description">\t\t\tAs a Formula car manufacturing company, we are
        not just interested in making cars but we aim to change the scenario of Motorsports racing in
        our country. With Srijan Formula Challenge, we aim to bring together all racing enthusiasts who
        share the same passion for race cars. This would provide a platform to all budding racers to test
        their mettle in the national arena.\n\n\t\t\tWe would be organising a minimum of 24 races annually
        with at least 2 races being held each month on the tracks of Kari Motor Speedway, Coimbatore,
        and MMSC Chennai, Tamil Nadu. In addition to the enthralling experience, the winner and the participants
        are in for exciting rewards and prizes.</string>

    <!-- model strings-->
    <string name="model_engine_title">Engine and Drivetrain </string>
    <string name="model_chassis_title">Chassis</string>
    <string name="model_suspension_title">Suspension</string>
    <string name="model_bodyworks_title">Bodyworks</string>
    <string name="model_electronics_title">Electronics</string>

    <!--TSI-17_SE Intro strings-->
    <string name="title_tsi17se">TSI-17-SE</string>
    <string name="intro_tsi17se">Professional or amateur. If you are looking for a car to meet the standard
        of your dream car that would set the tracks on fire, here is your stop! This model launched by our
        company is the epitome of innovation and engineering and does true justice to your passion.</string>
    <string name="engine_details_tsi17se">KTM Duke 390cc Engine (42 Bhp), Quaife Limited Slip Differential,
        Chain drive), paddle  shifter</string>
    <string name="chassis_details_tsi17se">Tubular Space frame chassis. 1020 AISI Mild steel</string>
    <string name="suspension_details_tsi17se">Double wishbone with Ohlins TTX36 damper, 10\” OZ racing wheels, 10\”
        Hoosier tires.</string>
    <string name="bodyworks_details_tsi17se">Carbon fiber bodyworks with CFRP seats and steering wheel.</string>
    <string name="electronics_details_tsi17se">In board Data Acquisition System with tunable ECU (5 Preloaded Maps).</string>
    <string name="price_tsi17se">Price : Rs.10,00,000</string>

    <!--TSI-17_SE Intro strings-->
    <string name="title_tsi17ke">TSI-17-KE</string>
    <string name="description_tsi_17ke">If you like tinkering with equipments in your garage and tweaking your car as per wishes,
        we present the perfect model for you. TSI-17 KE.\nThis model gives a chance to owners to work on their own car!\n
        The company provides all the standard, basic components in the form of a kit along with a complete tool set and a
        manual and it is upto the owner to build the car as per his whims! You also have a consulting engineer of our company
        at your disposal to help you build your dream car and get her roaring in the street.\nTSI-17 KE saves us assembly time as well as the transportation cost; so this model goes easy on the your wallet.
</string>
    
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
